Mob 2
~Rival~
Wait, was there an accident?
What the heck?
- He's bleeding.
- Whoa, this is bad.
Oh, God...
- Uh, I need to...
Seriously?
- This looks bad.
- Uh, I need to...
- A middle schooler? No way...
- Call...
- That was insanely loud.
- C-Call an a-ambulance...
What street is this?
He's not moving...
B-Bro...
Wh-What the? My phone...
H-Hey, bro?
(MOB MOB WOW!)
I realized that our youth is gray
The origin of this uneasiness
Is yet unknown
Trains of emotions keep running
Through my brain
Struggling through this adolescence
Don't disturb my deep psyche
Who is that behind you?
Opposing ideas creates distortion
Exorcise all the sorrow
So, do what you can now
My life
Finally, break it down
(Want) Both greed
(Young) And honesty
(Burn) Are growing
(1) On this chest of mine
(Trance) I'm not waking up
(Chance) I want to wake up
(Stance) These two different faces of mine
(1) Are standing back-to-back
Taking things as it is
In this free relation where
We resent each other
Once these two become one
That smile becomes one
And only "1"
(MOB MOB WOW!)
"1"
One and only "1"
(MOB MOB WOW!)
"1"
One and only "1"
Come on, Ly-chan. Hurry.
Okay.
Why the hell is there traffic here?
Hey, we're gonna be late.
I know...
Wh-What the?
An earthquake?
I don't know!
What's happening?
Hey, my phone's not working.
Hey, what the hell is this?!
What's going on?!
An earthquake?!
An explosion?!
What the hell?
Everyone in the area should follow
evacuation orders immediately.
Man, this earthquake sucks.
And it's long, too.
This says there are accidents and
crashes happening everywhere.
The cause is unknown. Most of the
major roads in Seasoning City...
are apparently backed up
due to restricted access.
Oh, looks like an evacuation
order's been issued.
Aw, but Shigeo was
gonna ask that girl out.
Yeah, that's not happening today.
Th-The suspect is around
160 centimeters tall...
Um... and wearing a school uniform
and h-holding a bouquet...
H-He's advancing... as he
destroys buildings around him...
Wh-Why...?
C-Come in!
Thank goodness I made it in time.
I had a hunch you'd be here,
so I flew over at the speed of light.
Pretty cool, huh?
So you're destroying everything you touch.
I'm not sure what happened,
but if I'd suffice, I'd be happy to lis...
Wait, seriously?!
Come on. Calm down.
Well? I've gotten stronger, too,
haven't I?
I thought I'd try a bit harder
after observing you.
Oh, you bought flowers! That's great!
But it might be a little dangerous
going as you are right now.
I'm not getting through to him?
You leave me no choice.
I'm gonna have to restrain you!
Sorry!
I'm gonna have to keep you restrained
until your powers calm...
Crap!
Ultimate Barrier!
The way you are right now...
reminds me of when we first met.
Kageyama...
Stop this.
You should head home for the day.
It's for your own good.
Kageyama taught me
something very important...
How I was the one who was average
for relying on these powers.
How important it is to accept yourself
without any psychic powers.
I can tell... that Kageyama
is trying to do just that.
Kageyama...
...isn't the kind of person
who'd hurt others!
He reacted!
If I destroy those...
Say, Kageyama...
You're not supposed to use your psychic
powers against others, right?
Something just came flying!
Hey, what the hell was that sound?!
Mommy!
Who the hell is this guy?!
He's destroying things as he walks?
Get away! He's dangerous!
Another earthquake!
I'm scared!
Not here, Kageyama!
There are people
who haven't evacuated yet!
- Kageyama's powers just keep growing...
- That's no human!
- I'm scared!
- Kageyama's powers just keep growing...
What can I do?
Everyone! It's dangerous here!
Please get to shelter immediately!
This is the epicenter of the disaster!
Please just get as far as you can!
Ly-chan!
Kageyama, are you
having some kind of episode?
To think you, of all people,
would go berserk
and lose control of your powers...
I guess you're pretty average, too!
I'm a bit relieved, honestly.
No...
Wait! There are still people here!
Help!
Daddy!
Mommy!
I don't want to die!
Someone help!
Look out!
What's going on?!
Save me!
Mommy! Help me!
Someone help!
I know this for sure...
I've been watching this whole time...
You're an absolutely gullible softy...
But you're still really strong...
And yet, you...
Back then...
When we first met...
You were crying by yourself.
I'm sure that's the case even now.
You're crying, aren't you, Kageyama?
Well?!
You want someone to stop you!
Don't you?!
Kageyama!
What...?
What's going on with me?
Hanazawa!
I can tell... that I did this.
I'm the one who did this...
to Hanazawa, too...
He tried everything he could to stop me
until he ended up like this?
There are times when things
don't work out...
It's fine if people laugh at you.
I'm average, too.
That's enough, Hanazawa-kun...
You don't have to think of this as me.
I can't stop this thing either.
You can fight back!
Yes! Use your powers against me!
But don't underestimate me!
I'm...
I'm your...
I'm your rival!
I guess I win this time!
Seriously, how many times
do I have to tell you?
Get a clue already, Koyama.
The items closer to expiry date
go front and center.
Is it that hard to understand?
If you don't, the old bentos...
All right, jeez!
I'm just trying to get our customers
the best products possible.
Have you ever witnessed the moment
a chicken pasta salad on display 3 hours ago
gets thrown in the trash?
Nothing in this world is darker than that.
Well, I can't sell old rice balls
to a customer with a smile.
Now, listen here. You need to
do as you're told sometimes.
Did you forget who recommended
you to the manager?
I'm grateful for what the
manager has done for me.
And that's exactly
why I'm gonna protect...
our store.
As I figured, all this destruction
was caused by an esper.
And he's headed right for
our convenience store.
Hey... That's that one shitty little brat!
What?!
I see... it all makes sense now.
Hey, you little brat! I have
no idea what's going on,
but I ain't gonna hold back
if you're coming for us!
Tch. He's not stopping.
Very well. Then we're going to have to act.
Telekinetic Helix!
Jugan: Oden Tongs!
After the incident
at Seasoning Apartments,
- many other buildings continue to crumble,
- That's not good...
I should've asked him
for his phone number.
Mob is going to show up, right?
Hey, look at this.
This is a picture of the incident
location posted online...
That's...
Could that be Lord Psycho Helmet?
It must be!
Wait, but why?
Captain! Isn't the guy in this picture...
It really isn't dying down.
I guess we better comply with
the evacuation orders, too.
What about Shigeo?
Whoa, there.
I can't get through to him.
I think his phone is off.
But we really don't need
to worry about Mob...
What's wrong?
R-Reigen! Look!
Mob?
Apparently, they've managed to evacuate
everyone including the elderly and children.
We can use as much of our
powers as we'd like.
Electronics aren't working in the area,
and the controls for vehicles, such as
cars and helicopters, stopped working.
So you'll be going down with parachutes.
If you're able to help with the situation,
they'll consider reducing your sentences,
so go do your best out there.
Don't forget that you're being
monitored at all times.
We're talking about one
measly esper kid, right?
We've got six. This'll be easy.
That's just based on eyewitness accounts.
Yeah, whatever.
You newbies are gonna
have to listen to us.
Just so you know, we get all the loot...
I'll go by myself.
The target can't be taken lightly.
You bastard!
- Kill! Kill! Kill!
- What the hell'd you do?!
Is the target someone you know?
I can feel his power...
growing even stronger.
Aw, jeez.
We should hurry. Open the back.
Be careful out there, Boss.
Hatori.
Hey, where's your parachute?
The blue light shined
Dazzling my eye at 01:30 AM
Even as I swiped the page over,
The smiles of friends besides me remain
Yes, I want someone to understand
All the colorless and transparent wishes
All the breath stuck within
The depth of my heart
Suddenly flowed out
Bringing my consciousness back
I remember the days hung dry
The very normal days passed by
Even if reality is corrupted
The sky we saw together
Was definitely real
It's harder to understand than
The grammar on the blackboard
The story that disappears
Under 24 hours makes me sad and lonely
It's so hard, and I find myself
On the verge of giving up again and again
But I...
The current me will no longer give up
Overflowing emotions on my sleeve,
Running through worry and doubt
Nobody has decided
if the future is 0 or 100,
So I'll paint over them myself
Even if my existence itself
can't be proven,
If this world struck me in my heart
I will flood it with cobalt blue
Brother, I haven't seen you
in that state for a while.
I'd always been afraid that this thing
would emerge from you again.
Next time onMob Psycho 100 III Episode 11:
"Mob 3 ~Trauma~."